Rohit Maharjan

Contact

106 Joseph St, Lidcombe 0424342832

Rohit.maharjan619@gmail.com

Objective

Experienced, skilful demonstrative history of working in customer service, Information Technology industry for more than 4 years. skilled in Customer service, Networking, Leadership, relation building, movie editing, Marketing. Education background in IT. Dedicated to professional performance and quality. Highly focused in growth and career development and very eager to learn new thing.

Education

Kings Own Institute (master's in information technology)
Infrastructure University (bachelors in information technology BCS.Hons)

Experience

Jul 2022- Running
Crown Contractor (Gaming Level 2 & Level 3)

Nov 2019 – Feb 2022 Junior React Developer • Trioplus Technologies

Feb 2019 – Nov 2019 3D Compositor • Incessant Rain Animation studio

Mar 2019 – Aug 2019 Whitehat Engineering • Marketing Manager

Key Skills

React.Js

Adobe.

Marketing
Project Management
JavaScript
SQL
Digital Marketing
Web Development

License & Certification

Automating Infrastructure on Google Cloud with Terraform – Google Cloud Skills Boost 2886304

Create Conversational AI Agent with Dialog flow CX – Google Cloud Skills Boost 2750052

Measure Site Reliability using Cloud Operations Suite Google Cloud Skills Boost 2831204

Hacker Rank Certified Python (Basic) – Hacker Rank 3105dcea1a12

Projects Completed

Simple Chat App from React and Firebase

Resort Website from React

Chat Server Project

References

Diana Apostolovski Crown (Key Account Manager) – 0484 347 098